# Serjeel Ranjan

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Hi, I am Serjeel Ranjan, a curious coder having skills in web dev and a will to learn anything new. I have some experience working in MERN Stack and have done various open source contributions. Please check my GitHub, LinkedIn and Competitive coding profiles to know more about me:)

### **Contacts**

Email: serjeelranjan@gmail.com

• Phone: 8946017321

• Address: Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

### **Social Accounts**

Github, LinkedIn, Website, Twitter

## **Technical Skills**

• Web Development: React, Node, MongoDB, SQL, HTML, CSS

Languages: Javascript, Python, Java, C

• Others: Git, GitHub

## Subject knowledge

- Blockchain and DeFi
- Data Structures and Algorithms (DSA)
- Database management system (DBMS)
- Object Oriented Programming (OOPs)

# **Competitive Coding Profile**

- Hackerrank (6\* Coder)
- Codeforces (pupil rated)
- GeeksForGeeks (Blog contributor)

# **Work Experience**

## ReactJS Intern (ongoing)

Company: Janus Softwares

• Duration: 03/2022 - Present

• Role: Frontend Developer

#### Full Stack Junior Dev (3.5 months)

Company: ProAct AI Consulting LLP

• Duration: 06/2021 - 09/2021

· Role: Full Stack Dev

Certificate of Completion: link

#### Wordpress Developer (5 months)

Company: Kanish Plaster PVT LTD

Duration: 01/2021 - 05/2021

• Role: Wordpress Developer / Content Writer

• Certificate of Completion and Offer Letter: link

## **Personal Projects**

#### My Portfolio Website

• Description: Totally not like any other portfolio website you must have ever seen before.

• Link: Website Link

• Github: Github Link

· Tools: ReactJS, SCSS, ThreeJS, Netlify

#### **Online Multiplayer UNO Game**

Description: A full stack game app made in React and Node.

Link: Website LinkGithub: Github Link

Tools: ReactJS, NodeJS, Socket.IO, Heroku

## **Freelance Projects**

#### **Checkmate Job Portal**

Description: A place to post/find jobs. A free/premium portal for job seekers and providers.

• Link: Website Link

· Tools: HTML, CSS, javascript, Django, sqlite

## **Education**

#### Bachelor of Engineering (B. Eng. or BE)

College: Kumaraguru College of Technology (Anna University)

• Duration: 06/2019 - Present

Course: Computer Science Engineering

Grade: 9.6GPA

#### 12th HSE (CBSE)

• School: Kendriya Vidyalaya 1 Tambaram Chennai

• Duration: 04/2016 - 03/2018

• Course: Physics, Chemistry, Maths, Computer Science

• Grade: 94%

## **Certifications**

### **Cisco Certified Networking Essentials**

Certificate: linkIssued: 12/2021

• Issuer: Cisco Networking Academy

### **Certificate for Completion of R Training**

Certificate: linkIssued: 06/2021

· Issuer: Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay

### **Problem Solving (Intermediate) Certificate**

Certificate: linkIssued: 02/2021Issuer: HackerRank

## Languages

• English: Full Professional Proficiency

• Hindi: Native

## **Interests**

· Fitness and Healthy Eating